https://christianbookproposals.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Skip to primary navigation Skip to content Skip to footerChristian Book ProposalsWriter/Author
Other Resources
Questions?
Create An Account
Sign In
Privacy Policy
ChristianBookProposals.com Service Privacy Policy
This website is operated and maintained by the Evangelical Christian Publishers Association (ECPA). This Privacy Policy describes ChristianBookProposals.com service policies and procedures for the collection of personal information by this site and our use and dissemination of all such information.
Our postal address is:
ECPA
5801 S. McClintock Dr.,
Ste. 104
Tempe, AZ 85283
How We Collect and Use Your Information
When you use our site, we collect biographical information including: name, address, phone, email address, present position, educational background and previous publications.
This information is viewed by our member publishers in their review process. This information will be used by the member publisher to make contact with you if they are interested in discussing your manuscript proposal.
This information is also viewed by the administrative staff of this site, employed by ECPA.
This information is NOT distributed or sold to any organizations. Only the staff and member publishers as mentioned above have access to this information for contact purposes only.
Payment Information
When a payment is made for the submission of a manuscript proposal, the payment information is secured by a 1,024-bit encryption. This provides a high level of security protection.
Links
The Christian Book Proposals site has established relationships with authors, book distributors and publishers that allow or visitors to our site to link directly to sites operated by these partners. These sites may collect personal information from you. This site is not responsible for the content or practices of web sites operated by third parties linked to our site. These links are meant for the user’s convenience only. Links to third party sites do not constitute sponsorship, endorsement, or approval by this site of the content, policies, or practices of such third party sites. Therefore, once you have left our sites via such a link, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party site.
E-mail Policy
Your email address will be used by administrative staff to provide you with occasional updates to this website. Your email address may also be used by a member publisher to make contact with you regarding your manuscript proposal only.
Policy That Applies to Children Under the Age of 13
ECPA appreciates the privacy concerns of parents and the importance of protecting the privacy of the information our sites collect from children. ECPA does not knowingly collect information from any child under the age of 13. Parents of children who visit our sites can be confident that any personal information that may be provided to our sites will be collected and maintained in accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act.
From time to time, ECPA may revise this Privacy Policy. Therefore, you should review it periodically so that you are up-to-date on our policies and practices.
The ChristianBookProposals.com website really simplified the proposal process.  The critique & edit service I used encouraged me every step of the way and only after a few months in the database, my proposal was picked up by a publisher!Dan Hochhalter, authorAfter three years of trying to get an agent, let alone a publisher to look at my manuscript, I gave this service a try. Within weeks I was contacted, and within months I was holding a contract. Let me encourage aspiring authors to don't give up! ChristianBookProposals.com is a great tool to help give your book the exposure it needs.Pastor Greg Dutcher, authorWhen you are a new, un-agented writer, getting a manuscript or even a proposal reading by a well-known publishing house can be extremely difficult. The ChristianBookProposals.com service bridged the distance between me and trusted publishing houses by providing a meeting ground that was truly the starting point for my career as a novelist.Susan Meissner, authorWe have secured two books on ChristianBookProposals.com. We regularly check the database and appreciate the professionally written proposals of interesting book ideas.Discovery House PublishersChristianBookProposals.com is a quick and easy way to find interesting projects.  We signed two authors from this site within twelve months and continue to check for new proposals on a regular basis.Bethany House/ Baker Publishing Group
ChristianBookProposals.com is the most efficient, cost-effective way for first-time authors to share their work with members of the ECPA, and for publishers to find exactly what they’re looking for. Everybody wins.Harvest House PublishersChristianBookProposals.com is a great tool for discovering new voices. We have already acquired a few titles for our digital-first line, and we regularly check the site for interesting submissions.David C CookFooter
Copyright © 2020.
All rights reserved.
Publishing OptionsWriting Your ProposalFinding an AgentWriters’ EventsOther Resources Back
Questions?Create An AccountSign In
× Close Panel
